cam4.ca 2017-01-20

# CAM4 Privacy Policy

##### CAM4 Privacy Policy

This Web site located at www.Cam4.com is owned by Surecom Corporation, NV, Curacao

Cam4.com provides its visitors with adult entertainment services collectively referred to as the Service. Because the success of our company is dependent on building and maintaining goodwill with our customers, we are committed to implementing measures designed to protect the privacy of those using our services.

Surecom Corporation, NV respects the privacy of all those who visit our web site and use our online services. Surecom Corporation, NV may collect information from the visitors to Cam4.com. This Privacy Policy governs your interaction with Cam4.com. Except as set forth within this Privacy Policy, we do not release personally identifiable information about the visitors to Cam4.com without their permission.

Please note that Surecom Corporation, NV reviews its privacy practices from time to time, and that those practices are, therefore, subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. To contact Surecom Corporation, NV about privacy issues, to report a violation of our Privacy Policy or to raise any other issue, please contact us at contact

**Surecom Corporation, NV gathers two types of information about users:**

Non-personally identifiable information: When visitors come to our web site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the web site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which hyperlinks were clicked. Collecting such information involves the logging of the IP addresses, operating system and browser used by each visitor to Cam4.com. Although such information is not personally identifiable, we can determine from an IP address a visitors Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of his or her point of connectivity.

We also use cookies - that is, small text files placed on a users computer hard drive to help us determine the type of content and sites to which a visitor to Cam4.com links, the length of time each visitor spends at any particular area of Cam4.com and the Cam4.com services visitors choose to use. Cookies also tell us which advertising a visitor has seen on our site. Essentially, cookies are a visitors identification card for the Surecom Corporation, NV computers, or servers, that placed them there. Cookies are only read by the server that placed them, and are unable to execute any code or virus. Cookies allow Surecom Corporation, NV to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at Cam4.com. Nevertheless, you should be able to control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser. For more information on how to do so, please refer to the documentation accompanying your browser.

Personally identifiable information: In certain areas of Cam4.com, we may require that you provide us with personally identifiable information (including for example a username, address, or email address).

**How We Use (and Do Not Use) the Information We Gather.**

Keep in mind that, while Surecom Corporation, NV encourages all third parties involved including but not limited to its affiliates and advertisers to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of the visitors to Cam4.com and to otherwise handle personal information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from Surecom Corporation, NV or independently. Nevertheless, in the event that you encounter any third party associated with, or who claims association with, Surecom Corporation, NV who you feel is improperly collecting or using information about you, please contact us here contact

Non-personally identifiable information: Surecom Corporation, NV uses non-personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of visitors to Cam4.com, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of Cam4.com. We provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We also use the aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. Cam4.com may contain links to other Internet web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites which may or may not be owned or operated by Surecom Corporation, NV. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including such sites use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when visitors to Cam4.com click through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites.

Personally identifiable information: From time to time, Surecom Corporation, NV may collect personally identifiable information from you via Cam4.com (including for example an email address). Surecom Corporation, NV limits its own e-mail solicitations to those Cam4.com visitors who have not opted out of receiving such communications. The solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail and provide the visitor with a method of opting out of receiving future communications of a similar nature.

We reserve the right to release information contained within our access logs concerning any Cam4.com visitor when that visitor partakes (or is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant or other court order, and to release such information in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests and as otherwise required by law. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement individuals or entities for investigation or prosecution.

Cam4 contacts you by email when we need to discuss your Cam4 account and any activity or promotions taking place on Cam4. We make it easy for you to opt out of these email messages at the time you register, or at any time thereafter through your profile settings. Cam4 provides you with the ability to opt out of all email or just certain types of messages. You may also opt out of email messages through the unsubscribe link provided at the bottom of all email correspondences. For more information, please contact us at support@cam4.biz.

**Google Analytics**

Cam4.com makes use of Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. The Cam4 site may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising features, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. We are required by Google to disclose the following information to you in our Privacy Statement in connection with our use of any Google Analytics for Display Advertising features on the Cam4 site:

  * You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads by using the Google Ads Settings page. You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on.
  * If the Cam4 site makes use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, Cam4 will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online and third party vendors, including Google, and may show Cam4 ads on sites across the Internet.
  * Cam4 and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to (a) inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user’s past visits to the Cam4 site, and/or (b) report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to Cam4.
  * Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by Cam4 to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to the Cam4 site, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes that will allow Cam4 to better serve you.

**Legal and Regulatory Requirements.**

We may disclose your personal information as necessary to meet legal, regulatory, insurance, audit, and security requirements, and as otherwise with your consent or as permitted or required by law. This may include lawful requirements to disclose personal information to government authorities domestically and in foreign countries. Government authorities may, without your consent (or our consent), communicate information to other authorities, including the police forces if there is reasonable cause to believe that a criminal or penal offence has been committed or is about to be committed. 

**Your Consent.**

By providing your personal information to us, you indicate that you agree and consent that we may collect, use, and disclose your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Statement. In addition, from time to time and where appropriate, we may request your specific authorization or consent for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purposes specified in our request. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. If you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your personal information, we may no longer be able to provide certain of our products or services.

Where we have provided or are providing services to you, your consent will be valid for so long as necessary to fulfill the purposes described in this Privacy Statement or otherwise at the time of collection, and you may not be permitted to withdraw consent to certain necessary uses and disclosures (for example, but not limited to, maintaining reasonable business and transaction records, disclosures to domestic and foreign government entities as required to comply with laws). We may also be required or permitted under statute or regulation to collect, use or disclose personal information without your consent, for example to comply with a court order, to comply with local or federal regulations or a legally permitted inquiry by a government agency, or to collect a debt owed to us.

**Changing or Deleting Personal Information; Business Transfers.**

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information that Surecom Corporation, NV collects via Cam4.com removed from Surecom Corporation, NV's database, please contact us at http://www.cam4.com/contact/ and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information collected via Cam4.com that will remain within Surecom Corporation, NV databases, access logs, backup files and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, Surecom Corporation, NV reserves the right, from time to time, to recontact former customers or users of Cam4.com.

In addition, we may sell or transfer assets or portions of our business as we continue to improve our product and service offerings. In such transactions, visitor information (whether non-personally identifiable or personally identifiable) may constitute one of the transferred business assets.

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to contact

Surecom Corporation NV | Landhuis Joonchi, Kaya Richard J Beaujon z/n | P.O. Box 837, Willemstad, Curacao | 00-5999-7331800
